yeah I think first of all they're
amazing tools right and I I highly
recommend in fact I think it's critical
for people to explore them and to use
them were relevant they're not without
their flaws but I think they are
absolutely a better way at least over
the Long Haul to develop software and
and they supercharge and there's a
reason so many developers fall in love
with them I think of let's maybe
separate the two so co-pilot and coding
assistant and a bunch of other tools I
think a lot of them are really in the
realm to me of AI assisted software
development and if if you think about
the the requirements to be able to
embrace those tools the threshold is
really quite low right these are
assistants they're not autonomous which
we can get to in a sec but also again
you're still working there in in the
same methodology and the same path and I
think when we think about AI native
software development we're thinking more
about did you even need to write that
code in the first place and once you
really level that up if you were to
develop software in that fashion what
does that mean in in how you build
software how you version software m